

Chunmei Shui

Frontend developer

Expertise Skill

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- React
- MYSQL
- HTML/CSS
- Git/GitHub

Education

- 2021-2022
 - HackYourFuture Denmark Full-stack Developer
- 0 2008-2011

SHANXI UNIVERSITY OF CHINESE TRADITIONAL MEDICINE

Work Experience

- Full-stack Developer2021-present
 - Javascript, React, Node.js, Mysql, Git/GitHub, html5,CSS
 - Meal-sharing, Weather report app
- Accounting Assistant2011-2015
 - checking Bills
 - calculate the financial bills. use SAP system clear payments, create invoices, and do bill discount

About me

After 10 years of graduating from university, I was keeping find the right and interesting job for myself. Luckily I found my career direction in frot-end developer, I finished HTML/CSS,React.js, JavaScript, Node.js, MySQL,git/GitHub, storybooks, postman, and swagger. courses in HYF in Denmark during the 9 months, and did some apps and projects with strong interest.

Language

- Mandarin
- English
- Danish

Contact Me

- +45 50309536
- chunmeishui578659@gmail .com
- Lundtoftparken, Lyngby
 Denmark